lindotjatji@gmail.com

0726477446 / 0614899718

PRETORIA, South Africa

0

An enthusiastic computer system engineering graduate, as a graduate I seek the opportunity to gain exposure and experience to develop and grow my career. I am a firm believer in developing quality software that have a lasting impact on its users and I excel in a team just as well as I do individually. My aim is to make a professional, dynamic contribution to my employer.

EDUCATION

O Study Program

Tshwane University of Technology

01/2015 - 11/2021

Courses

 Computer Systems engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack development: Learner The Digital Academy

12/2021 - Present

South Africa

Intern

E-bitz Electronics Engineering Solution

11/2020 - 08/2021

South Africa

Hardware assembling and testing raptors using a testing jig company.

- Achievements/Tasks
- Electronic hardware testing and assembly.
- Firmware development for electronic and network connected devices.
- Assisting community members with coding skills.
- Technical installations.

Learnership- Desktop support In2IT Technologies

02/2019 - 05/2019

South Africa

- · Achievements/Tasks
- Responding to client support requests.
- Installing and upgrading operating systems and computer software.

SKILLS

Analytical Thinking: Good at acquiring an understanding of a problem or situation.

Communication: Able to communicate complex information to individuals and groups.

Team Work: Able to contribute effectively towards the objectives of a team.

Computer Programming: Proficient programmer in C++, Angular2+, HTML, Postgres, SQL, CSS.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Raspberry Pi Vehicle Anti-theft Face Recognition System (07/2021)

CERTIFICATES

National Senior Certificate (12/2014)

National Diploma: Computer Systems Engineering (11/2021)

LANGUAGES

Sepedi

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Setswana

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Online games

Reading

Swimming